PAUL LEWIS: Welcome to this "Supercharged."
欢迎来到增压。
Now normally when we do our videos,
通常，当我们制作视频时，
we get lots of comments.
我们收到很多评论。
We get lots of questions on Twitter,
Twitter上的问题，
loads of things that kind of come into us.
许多这样的事情来到我们身边。
And so we thought, why not, let's actually
所以我们想，为什么不呢，让我们稍等一下，
take a step back and answer some of those questions.
我们回答其中一些问题。
How are SVGs rendered?
SVG如何呈现？
They seem quite slow.
看起来很慢。
Are they GPU accelerated?
GPU加速了吗？
If so, in what ways?
如果这是真的，那怎么会呢？
SURMA: I have actually no idea.
其实我不知道。
PAUL LEWIS: Cool, I do.
好，我知道。
So--
所以
--they're actually DOM elements.
-它们确实是DOM元素。
They--
嗯-
SURMA: Not only the SVG, put every child is an actual DOM
不只是SVG，还包括所有
element.
是的
SURMA: All the rectangle--
所有系统-
So you've got to be careful because if you move them
所以您应该小心，因为您
around, they're going to trigger layout.
我移动了它们，这将激发布局。
But the layer operation will stop at the SVG root.
但是，图层操作将停止SVG根目录。
That's one of the times we actually have
这是我们的时代之一
what we call a layout boundary where the layout actually
所谓的布局边界就是布局
is not document scoped.
它不在文档的中心。
It's going to be scoped to the SVG element.
它以SVG组件为中心。
SURMA: Would you look at that.
你能解释一下吗？
PAUL LEWIS: The other thing is a transform.
另一件事是转换。
Normally we promote this to its own layer
通常我们将其提升到自己的层，
and then transform it around.
然后我们将其转换。
That doesn't work in SVG context in Chrome.
这不适用于Chrome中的SVG上下文。
I'm not sure about other browsers.
不确定其他浏览器，
But in Chrome, we don't promote anything to its own layer
但是在Chrome中，我们不会将任何内容上传到其图层。
when you actually add will change or translates easier.
添加时，它很容易更改或翻译。
SURMA: So it's always a repaint?
所以它总是重新粉刷？
PAUL LEWIS: It's always a repaint.
它总是重新粉刷。
So you've got to be cautious with that.
所以您应该注意这一点。
SURMA: To be fair, I actually expected that for an SVG.
老实说，我对SVG期望如此。
Because for some reason, I think of it
因为出于某种原因，我考虑了一下，
more than canvas-like than anything else.
作为面料比什么都重要。
PAUL LEWIS: Right.
没错
But hopefully-- hopefully at some point,
但我希望-我希望它会在某个时候发展起来，
that optimization might [? land. ?] Don't know, though.
那个发展也许……尽管，我不知道。
And then are they GPU accelerated?
然后，他们加速了GPU吗？
They can be if you've got GPU rasterization switched on.
如果您具有激活的栅格化GPU密钥，它们就可以。
In fact, one of the best ways to improve SVG performance today
实际上，当今提高SVG性能的最佳方法之一是，
on mobile is to make sure that you've
在手机上肯定有...
got GPU rasterization, at least for Chrome.
至少适用于Chrome的GPU栅格化。
And where to get that, if you just
以及获得方式，搜索方式，
Google for-- I think it is actually magic
在Google上，我真的认为这就像魔术。
viewport Chromium, possibly.
可能是视口Chromium。
Or I think Ganesh or GPU rasterization Chrome.
或者我认为是Ganesh，或GPU光栅化Chrome
One of those will get you into the world
有人会带你走向世界，
that you need to be in.
你想成为的。
Next question-- is it possible to disable-- I don't
下一个问题：您能停下来吗-我不知道为什么...
know why they put it in quotes.
将它们放在引号中。
Is it possible to disable web animations
您可以关闭网络动画。
on very, very, very, very, very slow devices.
在非常非常非常慢的设备上。
So it has to be at least five.
所以你应该至少有五个。
And they put three tortoise emojis afterwards.
然后，他们将三只海龟作为表情符号。
SURMA: I think I know what that person's getting at.
我想我知道这个人的意思。
PAUL LEWIS: They're going for slow, going fully slow devices.
这意味着它们很慢，非常慢，这些设备。
I can't think of a way to adapt to your animations, really.
我真的想不出一种应对动画的方法。
SURMA: I think what you could do,
我认为您应该使用的是：
potentially the performance observer that
绩效观察员
is in the works, at the very least right now,
现在至少可以在Works上使用。
could eventually help you do this.
他最终可以帮助您做到这一点。
My first intuition when I read this question
当我阅读这个问题时，我的第一个直觉是
was that maybe you can kind of abuse request
可能是某种虐待
idle callback, because that will only be called if your web
requestIdleCallback，因为仅在页面为...时才应使用它。
page is not too busy.
不太忙
And if that is being called, you could use it
如果使用，则必须完成
to enable your web animations.
运行网络动画。
Go the other way around, have them disabled by default,
让我们扭转一下，默认情况下将其禁用
and basically enhance your web page with the animations,
她使用动画开发网页。
provided it is not under too much of a load.
前提是它们不会承受严重的压力。
PAUL LEWIS: The problem I had with that
我反对这种方式
is that your now main thread-- so if you're animating
现在您进入了主线程-如果您正在制作动画
with JavaScript, all your animations are
使用JavaScript，所有生成的动画将是
So you can then test for main thread availability
在这种情况下，您可以测试主线程的可用性
with requestIdleCallback or requestAnimationFrame or both.
使用idleCallback或请求AnimationFrame或同时使用两者。
But if you've got something that's like--
但是，如果您收到该表格的回复，
say there's this animation that is
假设您有动画
done with, say, a transition.
使用过渡实现
And you're just using the compositive thread.
而且您正在使用集成线程
And it's just going to keep going
将继续工作
even if the main thread is janked up,
即使主线不规则
then you can't use that technique because it's
您不能使用此技术，因为...
going to be like, well, I can't do any animations right now.
就像是“我现在不能做动画 。 ”
And the problem I have is that even with the frame timing API,
问题甚至在于帧定时API，
it's still only main thread availability.
在主线程中可用。
So it's kind of going to benefit anybody
因此它将有益于
who's animating JavaScript.
通过动画制作Java脚本。
But it's not going to benefit anybody
但这不会使那些做的人受益
who's animating just purely with, say, CSS
使用CSS进行动画制作
or something like that.
或类似的东西。
Overall, though, the thing I wanted to kind of ask myself
一般来说，问题仍然存在，
was, is it the right decision to disable the animations
停止动画是正确的决定吗？
in the first place?
来自基金会？
Because I was like, if your UX can stand not having
因为如果你的UX能承受
the animation, it feels like you don't need the animation.
缺乏动画似乎根本不需要它。
Animations just shouldn't be for the sake of, ideally.
我们不应该只为理想主义做动画。
SURMA: But usually they serve a point.
但是它们通常很有用，
And if they don't serve a point, then you
如果没有，那么
might as well skip them because it's
您总是可以忽略它们，因为它们
about being a little bit mindful about the user's resource.
通常对用户功能感兴趣。
PAUL LEWIS: Right.
是的
But again, it's a sliding scale and somebody
但是，在某些人看到的地方，它仍然不平衡，
might be like, hey, it's an added bonus if your device can
他们可能只将其视为可用扩展
take it or whatever.
以防您的设备负担得起。
As I say, I don't think you can do it reliably today.
正如我说的，我认为您现在不能依靠它们，
And I don't know of anything that's
也不涉及Works中存在的任何内容，
in the works that's just like, this is the cast iron
这是表达方式，例如：
way of saying, this device should be good to go.
“这个装置必须加强 。 ”
But I think you're right, requestIdleCallback is probably
但我认为您是对的，可能是requestIdleCallback
the closest we're going to get.
是我们可以走的最短路径。
Well, there you go.
好吧
So those are the questions that you asked.
这些是你问的问题，
And we would invite you to ask more questions in the comments
我们将邀请您在评论中提出更多问题，
below.
下面。
Twitter, I'm @aerotwist.
在Twitter上，我是aerotwist，
SURMA: @DasSurma.
我@ DasSurma
PAUL LEWIS: That's like The Surma,
那意味着：苏尔玛“死亡”，
but in German, which I learned.
但是你用德语学到了。
I'd forgotten all my German until--
我会忘记我对德语的一切了解，直到-
SURMA: I taught him.
你教过他
PAUL LEWIS: He did.
是的，他做到了。
He did.
他做到了。
So ask your questions.
好吧，问你问题。
Ping us on Twitter.
或在Twitter上写信给我们。
And we will catch you next time.
下次我们会与您联系。